Sea Cliff, NY • 516.455.6778

dave@davelevine.io • LinkedIn: davelevine87

IT Analyst with 7 years' experience and a master's degree in Information Systems.

Experienced IT analyst with comprehensive knowledge of developing, documenting and delivering solutions for attaining business goals. Capable of leading cross-functional teams to advance continuous improvement of web-based solutions for clinical faculty and staff.

Technical Proficiencies:

Platforms: Linux, MacOS, Windows

Tools: EC2, S3, AWS Identity & Access Management (IAM), Docker, XenServer

Methodologies: Software Development Life Cycle (SDLC), Agile Development

Certifications: AWS Certified Solutions Architect - Associate, Security+

Professional Experience

IT Business Analyst | Weill Cornell Medicine, New York, NY

December 2017 - Present

- Lead analyst and subject matter expert (SME) for the Conflicts of Interest module.
- Manage workflow of administrative approvals, training and documentations required for the advancement of over 5,000 research studies.
- Liaise with stakeholders to collect business requirements, create functional specifications, distribute data & interface with cross-functional teams.
- Conduct quality control testing used to improve workflows and enhance business processes.

Application Support Analyst II | Weill Cornell Medicine, New York, NY

October 2015 - December 2017

- Provided Tier 2 end-user support for research administration application modules.
- Provisioned user access rights to research administration application modules.
- · Collaborated with lead analysts in the implementation, testing & training for new and enhanced functionality.
- Created and developed knowledge base to store documentation, procedures & solutions related to research administration application modules.

Systems Support Analyst | ClickIT Inc., Hauppauge, NY

November 2013 – October 2015

- Provided Tier 1 end-user support for MS Windows based system support & proprietary surveillance software.
- Conducted video analytics testing to improve motion detection, heat maps & people counting.
- Created and maintained company knowledge base.

Education

Master of Science in Information Systems

Graduated 2014

Long Island University, New York, NY

Bachelor of Science in Information Management & Technology

Graduated 2011

Long Island University, New York, NY

Additional Skills